<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Commentaries on Sainpse Institute.</title>
    <link>sainpse.github.io/commentary/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Commentaries on Sainpse Institute.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="sainpse.github.io/commentary/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>he History of Artificial Intelligence: From Ancient Myths to Modern Technologies</title>
      <link>sainpse.github.io/commentary/ai/commentary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>sainpse.github.io/commentary/ai/commentary/</guid>
      <description>
Introduction Definition of artificial intelligence Overview of the history of AI Ancient History Mythical stories and legends about intelligent machines Early philosophical discussions of the possibility of creating intelligent machines The Early Modern Period The development of mechanical calculators and other automated devices The emergence of cybernetics and the concept of feedback control The Birth of Artificial Intelligence The development of the first digital computers and their impact on AI research The creation of the first AI programs and algorithms The AI Boom The rapid development of AI in the 1980s and 1990s The emergence of machine learning and neural networks The AI Winter and Revival The slowdown in AI research in the late 1990s and early 2000s The resurgence of AI in the 2010s thanks to advances in big data, cloud computing, and deep learning The Present and Future of AI Current applications of AI in fields such as healthcare, finance, and transportation Challenges and ethical concerns related to AI Predictions for the future development of AI Conclusion Recap of the key milestones in the history of AI Reflection on the past, present, and future of AI </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computation</title>
      <link>sainpse.github.io/commentary/computation/commentary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>sainpse.github.io/commentary/computation/commentary/</guid>
      <description>Hugo is the world’s fastest framework for building websites. It is written in Go.
It makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.com/russross/blackfriday https://github.com/alecthomas/chroma https://github.com/muesli/smartcrop https://github.com/spf13/cobra https://github.com/spf13/viper Learn more and contribute on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
